droiddog.com 2011-12-03

# Privacy policy | DroidDog Android Blog

droiddog.com provides this Privacy Policy to inform visitors of our privacy practices and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from visitors to our website. droiddog.com respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you may share with us. You can generally browse droiddog.com without giving us any information about yourself, but in the event you do share any information with us this Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
Generally, when you browse droiddog.com you does so anonymously. There are certain visitors to droiddog.com who choose to interact with us in ways that require us to collect personal information. You may provide personal information to droiddog.com in one of the following ways: (1) by sharing contact information when using the “Contact Us” form, (2) by sharing contact information when using the “Submit News” form or (3) by sharing personal information when posting a comment.

When you visit droiddog.com from a computer, mobile phone or other device, we may collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. Information collected include operating system, browser type, screen resolution, location, Internet Protocol (IP) address, as well as the Web pages you visit.

**Cookie Information**  
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you’ve visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Some parts of droiddog’s website may use cookies to track user traffic patterns in order to determine the usefulness of our website information and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of droiddog’s website if you do so. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through many parts of our website.

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use your information to help us improve our services, fulfill any requests you may have and to communicate with you. droiddog.com does not rent or sell personal information about you. Personal information we may collect such as your name and email address that you use when contacting us via the “Contact Us” form or “Submit News” form will not be used for any reason other than for the purpose of responding to your inquiry.

**Comment Policy**  
droiddog.com encourages comments, questions, and suggestions from our visitors. If any comment is posted to droiddog.com in violation of this comment policy, droiddog.com reserves the right to edit or delete comments for any reason we deem appropriate. Any comment posted to droiddog.com will be made visible to the public and can be reproduced, published, broadcast, or posted outside of droiddog. If you contribute to droiddog.com in the comment section, we ask that you adhere to the guidelines outlined below:

  1. Topic Relevancy: Please keep all comments relevant to the article you are commenting on. Comments that are considered off topic are subject to deletion.
  2. Spam: Spam and any comments that are considered advertisements will be deleted.
  3. Profanity: Please avoid using any kind of profanity when commenting. Comments that include profanity are subject to deletion.
  4. Personal Attacks: Please respect the views and opinions of other readers. Personal attacks will not be tolerated. Comments that personal attack readers, authors, or any other individual will be deleted.
  5. Hate Speech: Hate speech will not be tolerated. Comments that include racism, sexism, homophobia, or any other kind of hate speech will be deleted.
  6. Illegal Content: Please do not post any comments that involves illegal content. This include links to third-party websites. Comments that include illegal content will be deleted.
  7. Other: Comments that might violate our [Terms of Use](http://www.droiddog.com%20/terms-of-use/) are subject to deletion.

**Third-Party Services**  
droiddog.com uses Google Analytics to help us understand how people navigate our website. Through Google, Analytics collects the information sent by your browser as part of a Web page request, including cookies and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. This information is also received by Google and their use of the information collected is governed by their [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html).

**Third-Party Websites**  
droiddog.com contains links to other websites, but we do not exercise any control over third-party websites. Third-party websites may place their own cookies, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites so we encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those websites.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
droiddog.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available on this Web page.
